rank10.org 2015-09-06

# Page Rank Checkcer - rank10.org

Please read this privacy statement carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal information and how we will treat it. This privacy policy is applicable to websites falling under the primary holder rank10.org. 

  1. **How we collect information about you**

When you visit the rank10.org website, we collect your IP address and standard web log information, such as your browser type and the pages you accessed on our website. 

Before permitting you to use our Service, we may require you to provide additional information we can use to verify your identity or address or manage risk, such as your date of birth, social security number or other information. We may also obtain information about you from third parties such as credit bureaus and identity verification services. 

Finally, we may collect additional information from or about you in other ways not specifically described here. For example, we may collect information related to your contact with our customer support team or store results when you respond to a survey. 

  2. **How we use cookies**

When you access our website, we, or companies we hire to track how our website is used, may place small data files called "cookies" on your computer. 

We send a "session cookie" to your computer when you log in to your account. This type of cookie helps us to recognize you if you visit multiple pages on our site during the same session, so that we don't need to ask you for your password on each page. Once you log out or close your browser, this cookie expires and no longer has any effect. 

We also use longer-lasting cookies for other purposes such as to display your preferred pages for you, so that you don't need to retype or change each time. 

We encode our cookies so that only we can interpret the information stored in them. You are free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but doing so may interfere with your use of our website. 

  3. **How we protect and store personal information**

Throughout this policy, we use the term "personal information" to describe information that can be associated with a specific person and can be used to identify that person. We do not consider personal information to include information that has been anonymized so that it does not identify a specific user. 

We store and process your personal information on our computers in the Japan, and we protect it by maintaining physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable Japanese  regulations. We use computer safeguards such as firewalls and data encryption, we enforce physical access controls to our buildings and files, and we authorize access to personal information only for those employees who require it to fulfill their job responsibilities. 

  4. **How to Control Your Privacy**

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms. 

  5. **Special Note About Google Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies (Google, Inc.) to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google's cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google's own privacy policies. 

  6. **What is the DoubleClick DART cookie?**

The [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

  7. **How to Contact Us**

Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to us for further clarification. 

Email: team@rank10.org 

Your IP Address  
204.236.235.245
